A Guide to the Richmond (Va.), Bureau of Permits and Inspections, Building permit architectural blueprints and specifications, 1907-1976
Library of Virginia
- Blueprint drawings, 1907-1950, 3167 sets of blueprints
  - Office Buildings, 1909-1948
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 18898 (?), Building for Mr. O. D. Brinser, Address: 1600 Block Hull St., 1928 (Folder 1606)
      Drawn by: Courtenay S. Welton, Architect, 701 Grace - American Building, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: O. D. Brinser; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 16311A, Remodeling for a Brick Office Building for the National Ideal Benefit Society, Address: 210 E. Cary St., 1928 (Folder 1612)
      Drawn by: Charles T. Russell, Architect; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Ideal Benefit Company; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 18948, Office Building for Davis Brothers, Incorp'd., Address: 15 N. 6th St., 1928 (Folder 1611)
      Drawn by: L. Otis Spiers, Architect, Richmond, Va., Bascom J. Rowlett, Assoc. Arch't; Contractor: Davis Bros.; Commissioned by: Davis Bros.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 17082A, Grace Street Telephone Building [additions and alterations], Address: 705 E. Grace St., 1928 (Folder 1727)
      Drawn by: Voorhees Gmelin & Walker Architects, 1343 H Street N. W., Washington, D. C.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Co.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 19897, Grace Street Telephone Building, S. E. Corner of Grace & Seventh Streets, Address: 701, 703 E. Grace St., 1929 (Folder 1744)
      Drawn by: Voorhees, Gmelin & Walker, Architects, 1343 H Street N. W., Washington, D. C.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Company of Virginia; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 18295A, Alterations to Building 12th & main Sts, Address: 1200 E. Main St., 1930 (Folder 1804)
      Drawn by: Carneal, Johnston & Wright, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Commonwealth of Virginia, Department of Motor Vehicles; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 18545A, Additions to Professional Building, Address: 501 E. Franklin St., 1930 (Folder 1796)
      Drawn by: Marcellus E. Wright, Architect, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Professional Building Corp.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 21289, Extension and Remodeling - United States Post Office, Court House, and Customs House, Address: 1000 E. Main St., 1930 (Folder 1778)
      Drawn by: James A. Wetmore, Acting Supervising Architect, Treasury Department, Office of the Supervising Architect, Washington, D. C.; Contractor: National Construction Company; Commissioned by: United States Government; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 18446A, Alterations and Additions to Office Building, N.W. Corner 3rd. & Clay Sts., Southern Aid Society of Virginia, Inc., Address: 504 N. 3rd. St., 1930 (Folder 1791)
      Drawn by: Edw. F. Sinnott, Architect, American Bank & Trust Bldg., Richmond, Va.; Contractor: John T. Wilson and Company; Commissioned by: Southern Aid Society; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: N/A, Business Building for Mr. W. J. Coulter, Address: N/A, 1931 (Folder 1820)
      Drawn by: Fred. A. Bishop, Architect, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: W. J. Coulter; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 21833, Office and Private Garage Bldg. 2400 North Lombardy St. for Dr. Wm. F. Gregg, Address: 2400 N. Lombardy St., 1931 (Folder 1879)
      Drawn by: Henry T. Barnham, Architect & Engineer, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: William F. Gregg; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 19003A, Plan for Remodeling of Building at Vine and Main Streets - The Womble Motor Company, Address: 1630 W. Main St., 1931 (Folder 1816)
      Drawn by: Allen J. Saville, Inc., 607 Electric Building, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Virginia Electric and Power Co.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 19236A, Alterations to Building, 7th and Grace Sts., Address: 700 E. Grace St., 1931 (Folder 1891)
      Drawn by: Carneal, Johnston & Wright, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Seventh Street Realty Corp.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 23640, Brick and Concrete Commercial Building, No. 2 South Fifth St., for Powers and Anderson Incorporated, Address: 2 S. 5th St., 1936 (Folder 1981)
      Drawn by: I. T. Skinner, Architect; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Powers - Anderson Inc.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 23180A, Alterations to Building, Home Beneficial Assoc.., 9th & Broad Sts., Address: 900 E. Broad St., 1936 (Folder 1954)
      Drawn by: Carneal, Johnston & Wright, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Home Beneficial Association; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 22785A, Alterations and Additions to 911 E. Main St., Address: 911 E. Main St., 1936 (Folder 1978)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Clarence Milhiser Estate; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 23712, Garage and Office for the Yellow Cab Company of Virginia, Inc., Address: 1834 W. Cary St., 1936 (Folder 1974)
      Drawn by: H. Carl Messerschmidt, Architect, 1124 Mutual Building, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: O. D. & Ben Dennis; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 23730, Office Building for Jones & Robins, 615 E. Franklin St., Address: 615 E. Franklin St., 1936 (Folder 1967)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Franklin Holding Co.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 22787A, Alteration to Present Bldg., Tenth & Byrd Sts., Address: 213 - 215 South 10th St., 1936 (Folder 1966)
      Drawn by: Allen J. Saville, Inc., Contractors, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Southern States Cooperative, Inc.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 23749, Office Building for Richmond Sand & Gravel Corpn., Address: 3011 Dock St., 1936 (Folder 1976)
      Drawn by: Edward F. Sinnott, Architect, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Richmond Sand & Gravel Co.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 23821, Office Building for Taylor Brothers, Address: 6 South 5th St., 1936 (Folder 1956)
      Drawn by: Carl M. Lindner, Architect, State & City Bank Bldg., Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Edgar R. Lafferty & W. G. Taylor; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 23293A, Office Building for Export Leaf Tobacco Co., Address: 801 Bowe St., 1936 (Folder 1961)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Export Leaf Tobacco Co.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 24180A, Studios for WRNL, Address: 323 E. Grace St., 1937 (Folder 2033)
      Drawn by: Baskervill & Son, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: News - Leader Co. (Radio Station WRNL); Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 23804A, Alterations to State Planters Bank Bldg. For [radio] Station WRTD, Address: 900 E. Main St., 1937 (Folder 2012)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: State Planters Bank & Trust Co.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 23763A, Alterations to Building, 1111 E. Main St., for Lawyers Title Ins. Co., Address: 1111 E. Main St., 1937 (Folder 2008)
      Drawn by: Carneal, Johnston & Wright, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Lawyers Title Insurance Corp.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 24186A, Studios for WRNL - Air Conditioning Equipment, Address: 323 E. Grace St., 1937 (Folder 1996)
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 24647, A Building for the Richmond Broadcasting Co., Inc., to be Located on S. W. Corner Broad and Tilden Sts., Address: 3301 W. Broad St., 1938 (Folder 2177)
      Drawn by: N/A; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Richmond Broadcasting Co.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 25037A, Fourth Floor Addition to Broad - Grace Arcade, Address: 216 - 226 E. Grace St., 1938 (Folder 2042)
      Drawn by: A. O. Budina, Architect, 1013 A, E. Main St., Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Broad - Grace Arcade Corp.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 25898A, Alterations and Additions to News Leader Arcade Building, Address: 319 - 321 E. Grace St., 1939 (Folder 2120)
      Drawn by: Baskervill & Son - Architects; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: The News Leader Co.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 25368A, American Tobacco Co., 2009 East Grace St., Address: 2009 E. Grace St., 1939 (Folder 2088)
      Drawn by: Marcellus Wright & Son, Architects, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: American Tobacco Co.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 25265, Sales and Distribution Building, The Curles Neck Dairies, Address: 3302 W. Broad St., 1939 (Folder 2098)
      Drawn by: Louis W. Ballou, Architect, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: A. B. Ruddock; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 25596, Building for the Virginia Commission for the Blind, Address: 3003 Parkwood Ave., 1940 (Folder 2187)
      Drawn by: J. Binford Walford, Architect; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Virginia Commission for the Blind; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 28189A, Office Building for Nolde Bros., Inc., Address: 2518-20 E. Broad St., 1942 (Folder 2296)
      Drawn by: J. Edwin Hopkins, Architect and Bakery Engineer; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Nolde Bros., Inc.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 27884A, Office Building for Export Leaf Tobacco Co., Address: 800 Bowe St., 1942 (Folder 2242)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: E. L. Bass Bros.; Commissioned by: Export Leaf Tobacco Co.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 26642, Office Building for Nolde Bros, Inc., Address: 2520 E. Broad St., 1942 (Folder 2268)
      Drawn by: J. Edwin Hopkins, Architect and Bakery Engineer; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Nolde Brothers, Inc; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 28745A, Reynolds Metal Building, Address: 301 E. Grace St., 1943 (Folder 2301)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Reynolds Metal Co.; Notes: These drawings are blueline prints
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 26829, Employees Service Building for Richmond Engineering Co, Inc., Address: 7th and Hospital Sts., 1943 (Folder 2307)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Richmond Engineering Co, Inc.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 30662A, Changes in Office of P. Lorillard Co., Address: 2300 E. Cary St., 1944 (Folder 2332)
      Drawn by: Carneal, Johnston & Wright, Architects and Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: P. Lorillard Co.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 30139A, Fire Escape, Address: 6th and Franklin Sts., 1944 (Folder 2340)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: C & P Telephone Co.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 29798A, American Building, Address: 10th and Main Sts., 1944 (Folder 2336)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Chelsia Richmond Corp.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 33348A, [General Electric Supply], Address: 4th & Canal Sts., 1945 (Folder 2443)
      Drawn by: R. E. Cumming; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: General Electric Supply; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 27466, Studios for Station WLEE, Address: 1705 Colorado Ave., 1945 (Folder 2382)
      Drawn by: Courtenay S. Welton, Architect, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: Doyle and Russell; Commissioned by: T. G. Tinsley; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 31619A, Alterations in the Grace Street, Randolph and Madison Telephone Buildings., Address: 703-05-11 E. Grace St., 1945 (Folder 2346)
      Drawn by: [Engineering Department, Chesapeake & Potomac Telephone Co. of Virginia]; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: C & P Telephone Co.; Notes: Grace Street (703), Randolph (705), and Madison (711)
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 27668, Office Building for R. E. Richardson & Sons, Inc., Address: 2100 Westwood Ave., 1945 (Folder 2487)
      Drawn by: Louis W. Ballou and Charles C. Justice, Architects, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: R. E. Richardson & Son; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 27582, Drawings of Buildings for Magnolia Frozen Foods, Inc., Address: 5505 Patterson Ave., 1945 (Folder 2495)
      Drawn by: Courtenay S. Welton, Architect, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: James Fox and Sons; Commissioned by: Magnolia Frozen Foods; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 33124A, Addition to Offices for Richmond Dairy Co., Address: 314 N. Jefferson St., 1945 (Folder 2507)
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 27445, Building for Experiment, Inc., Address: 9th St. Rd., 1945 (Folder 2390)
      Drawn by: Louis W. Ballou, Architect, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Experiment Inc.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 33800A, Alterations and Additions to Office, Ruffin & Payne Inc., 1701 5th Ave., Address: 1701 Fifth Ave., 1946 (Folder 2549)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Ruffin & Payne; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 33854A, Westinghouse Electric Co., Alterations to Office, Address: 6th and Byrd Sts., 1946 (Folder 2545)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: J. Kennon Perrin Co., General Contractors; Commissioned by: Westinghouse Electric Supply Co.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 27804, Laundry Building for Stork Diaper Service, S. E. Corner Moore & High Point Sts., Address: 3119 Moore St., 1946 (Folder 2413)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Davis and Spires, Inc.; Commissioned by: Stork Diaper Service; Notes: Includes two letters regarding joist spacing.
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 33460A, Alterations to 810 W. Franklin Street, Address: 810 W. Franklin St., 1946 (Folder 2409)
      Drawn by: Marcellus Wright & Son, Architects, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Dr. James Blades; Notes: Plot plan shows surrounding buildings on W. Franklin Street and their names and/or uses. CD # 154.
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 34023, Richmond Press Building, Address: 207 Governor St., 1946 (Folder 2464)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Worsham & Lincke; Notes: Doesn't have A at end of Permit Number, but says in specifications "for remodeling third floor" to "convert it from warehouse space to office space"
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 34088A, Rearrangement of 5th Floor, Presbyterian Committee of Publication, Address: 8 N. 6th St., 1946 (Folder 2454)
      Drawn by: J. Binford Walford, O. Pendleton Wright, Architects, 103 East Cary Street, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Presbyterian Committee of Publications; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 34132A, Addition to Office Building and Warehouse, VA Gas Industries, Inc., Address: 1623 Brook Rd., 1946 (Folder 2438)
      Drawn by: Louis W. Ballou and Charles C. Justice, Architects, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: VA Gas Industries; Notes: Also contains Foundation Plan for L. P. Gas Storage Tanks by the Richmond Engineering Co., Inc.
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 27866, Office Building, Address: 605-7 E. Main, 1946 (Folder 2561)
      Drawn by: A. O. Budina, Architect, 1013 - A East Main St., Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Gramon Corp.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 33664A, Alterations to 1225 W. Broad St., Address: 1225 W. Broad St., 1946 (Folder 2412)
      Drawn by: Baskervill & Son, Architects, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Crane & Co.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 28064, Residence and Office, Lombardy Street, Dr. S. Melworth, Address: 2322 N. Lombardy St., 1946 (Folder 2481)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Floyd Wilkerson, General Contr.; Commissioned by: Samuel Melworth; Notes: Residence and Office
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 34250A, Lawyers Title Building, Address: 1109-11 E. Main St., 1946 (Folder 2619)
      Drawn by: Marcellus Wright & Son, Architects, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Lawyers Title Ins. Co.; Notes: Specifications for concrete fire vault in the rear.
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 33843A, Alteration and Additions, Bam's Inc., Address: 311 E. Broad St., 1946 (Folder 2717)
      Drawn by: Slaughter, Saville & Blackburn, Inc., Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Bam's Inc.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 28398, Standard Oil of New Jersey, Virginia Division, Address: 3715 W. Broad St., 1946 (Folder 2699)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Standard Oil Company; Notes: [Scanned images of some of the drawings available on Photo Lab #10_1252]
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 34301A, Office Building Alterations for Southern States Cooperative, Address: 7th and Main, 1946 (Folder 2635)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Southern States; Notes: Remodeling the Old Richmond Trust Building
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 34671A, Alterations to 406 E. Broad Street, Equitable Loan Society, Inc., Address: 406 E. Broad St., 1947 (Folder 2823)
      Drawn by: Staley & Taylor, Architects, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Equitable Loan; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 34615A, Alterations and Additions to Bldg, Universal Life Insurance Co., Address: 116 S. 3rd St., 1947 (Folder 2821)
      Drawn by: Carl M. Lindner; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Universal Life; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 28717, Office Building for Virginia-Carolina Chemical Corp., Address: 405 E. Main St., 1947 (Folder 2722)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: J. Kennon Perrin Co., Contractors; Commissioned by: Virginia-Carolina Chemical Co.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 34673A, Alterations to Mutual Building, Richmond, Henrico County, Virginia, Address: 9th and Main St., 1947 (Folder 2830)
      Drawn by: Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Comjpany Chief Engineers Office; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Mutual Assoc. Society; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 28742, Studio and Office Building for Richmond Radio Corporation, Address: 111 N. 4th St., 1947 (Folder 2687)
      Drawn by: Carneal & Johnston, Architects & Engineers, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Richmond Radio Corp.; Notes: Plans include several detailed drawings regarding the structural work by Blaw-Knox Division of Blaw-Knox Co, Pittsburgh
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 34563A, Alterations and Additions to 106 E. Cary St., for Eastern Builders Supply Co, Inc., Address: 106 E. Cary St., 1947 (Folder 2667)
      Drawn by: Louis W. Ballou and Charles C. Justice, Architects, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Eastern Builders Supply; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 34606A, Addition to Laundry Building for Florsheim Laundry and Dry Cleaning Corp., Address: 1208 N. Boulevard, 1947 (Folder 2886)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Aubrey H. Straus; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 29891, Mechanical Building, Richmond Newspapers Incorporated, Address: 107 N. 3rd St., 1948 (Folder 3148)
      Drawn by: Baskervill & Son, Architects, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Richmond Newspapers; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 34871A, Alterations and Additions in Boiler Room, Bell Telephone Building, Grace Street, Address: 703 E. Grace St., 1948 (Folder 3009)
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 29768, Office Building for Southside Brick Works, Incorporated, Barnes Siding, Address: 2220 Concord St., 1948 (Folder 3032)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Southside Brick Works, Inc.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 29310, Proposed Office Building for The Bernie Corporation, 811 East Franklin Street, Address: 811 E. Franklin St., 1948 (Folder 2994)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: Thorington Const. Co.; Commissioned by: Bernie Corp.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 34930A, Proposed Alteration to 207 N. Foushee Street, for Richmond Dental Laboratory, Address: 207 N. Foushee St., 1948 (Folder 3126)
      Drawn by: H. Carl Messerschmidt, Architect, 1124 Mutual Building, Richmond VA; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Richmond Dental Lab; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 35133A, Radio Supply Company, Address: 3302 W. Broad St., 1948 (Folder 3033)
      Drawn by: Bowker and Roden, Inc., Office and Plant, Westwood Ave. West of R. F. & P. R. R., Dial 6-0765, Richmond, VA; Contractor: James Fox and Sons; Commissioned by: Radio Supply Co.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 29642, [Office building], Address: 1400 Roseneath Rd., 1948 (Folder 2947)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Atlantic Bitulithic Co.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 34869A, Richmond, Virginia, 17 North 7th Street Building, Alterations, Address: 17 N. 7th St., 1948 (Folder 2959)
      Drawn by: Chesapeake and Potomac Telephone Co. of VA Engineering Dept.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: C & P Telephone Co.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 29641, Office Building for The Burnie Corporation, Nos. 7, 9, 11, 11 1/2 North Third Street, Address: 9 N. Third St., 1948 (Folder 2931)
      Drawn by: W. H. Pringle, Architect; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Bernie Corp.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 29684, Building for the Union Life Insurance Co, Inc., Address: 11-13 N. 6th St., 1948 (Folder 3116)
      Drawn by: Merrill C. Lee, F. A. I. A, Architect, Richmond, VA; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Union Life Insurance Co.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 34972A, Alterations to Building, 840 W. Grace Street, For Dr. Jacob Moore, Address: 840 W. Grace St., 1948 (Folder 3083)
      Drawn by: John Stafford Efford, Architect, Central National Bank Building, Richmond, Virginia; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Dr. Jacob Moore; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 29571, Office Building, Richmond Lumber and Building Supply Company, East 4th Street at Maury St., Address: 325 E. 4th St., 1948 (Folder 2918)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Mrs. Fannie Perel; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 35064A, Alterations to 1209 Hull Street for H. V. Baldwin and Co., Inc., Address: 1209 Hull St., 1948 (Folder 2933)
      Drawn by: H. Carl Messerschmidt, Architect, 1124 Mutual Building., Richmond, Va.; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: H. V. Baldwin and Co.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 29540, Mrs. Gussie Salsbury, Stove Building, North Road and Mosside Ave., Address: 4201-4209 North Ave., 1948 (Folder 2916)
      Drawn by: Unsigned; Contractor: N/A; Commissioned by: Mrs. Gussie Salsbury; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 35081A, Bell Telephone Building, Grace St., Addition, Address: 703 E. Grace St., 1948 (Folder 3114)
      Drawn by: Merrill C. Lee, Architect, Richmond, Va.; Contractor: Doyle, Russell and Wise Contracting Co., Inc.; Commissioned by: C & P Telephone Co.; Notes:
    - Office Building - Permit Number: 29390, Commonwealth Sales Corp., Greensville, N.C., Building Cor[ner] McTavish and Norfolk Sts., Address: 3300 Norfolk St., 1948 (Folder 3138)